question_data = [{"category": "Software Development",
                  "topic": "Agile",
                  "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "Robert is working as a Test Manager at TPT Limited. James an intern working with Robert suggest for testing only once at the end of the project instead of testing continuously. What should be Robert's response in this case?",
                  "correct_answer": "Explain to them the cost of finding defects at the end of a project can be massive and outweigh the cost of testing incrementally throughout the project.",
                  "incorrect_answers": ["Accept this and add a few sprints at the end of the project for testing and bug fixing.", "Ask them to test at least the most important features.", "Accept this and have the development team test the project themselves."]},

                 {"category": "Software Development",
                  "topic": "Agile",
                  "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "The primary advantages of using Agile over traditional methods, is _________________.",
                  "correct_answer": "Increased customer satisfaction through regular feedback.",
                  "incorrect_answers": ["Agile gives instant benefit.", "No planning is required.", "The same work can be completed with fewer developers."]},

                 {"category": "Software Development",
                  "topic": "Agile",
                  "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "_____________ is not a stage in Tuckman’s model of group development.",
                  "correct_answer": "Initiating",
                  "incorrect_answers": ["None of these", "Storming", "Forming"]},

                 {"category": "Software Development",
                  "topic": "Agile",
                  "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "Select the roles prescribed by the Kanban development method.",
                  "correct_answer": "Neither Product Owner. or Development team",
                  "incorrect_answers": ["Development team.","Both Product Owner. and Development team", "Product Owner."]},

                 {"category": "Software Development",
                  "topic": "Agile",
                  "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "Non-engagement of business users with the developers may lead to ________________.",
                  "correct_answer": "All of these",
                  "incorrect_answers": ["Wrong products development", "Products not meeting the requirements", "Lack of trust between developers and the business users"]},

                 {"category": "Software Development",
                  "topic": "Agile",
                  "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "How does Agile score over Waterfall projects?",
                  "correct_answer": "Agile can cope with complex changing environments.",
                  "incorrect_answers": ["Agile cannot cope with chaotic or disordered environments.", "Agile removes the need for documentation.", "Agile projects do not use any planning."]},

                 {"category": "Software Development",
                  "topic": "Agile",
                  "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "POOGI stands for _________________.",
                  "correct_answer": "Process Of Ongoing Improvement.",
                  "incorrect_answers": ["Process Of Ongoing Interactions.", "Process Of Ongoing Involvement.", "Process Of Ongoing Iterations."]},

                 {"category": "Software Development",
                  "topic": "Agile",
                  "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "What should be the course of action when a Scrum team discovers their inability to complete the stories included in their sprint, during a daily stand-up?",
                  "correct_answer": "Approach the Product Owner and negotiate the scope of the lowest priority stories.",
                  "incorrect_answers": ["Quietly schedule a few late nights hoping to finish the work on time.", "Bring a few extra people into the team to help them complete all of the stories.", "Decide to de-scope the lowest priority stories."]},

                 {"category": "Software Development",
                  "topic": "Agile",
                  "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "What is the disadvantage of using MoSCoW prioritization?",
                  "correct_answer": "Most of the stories get prioritized as “must do”.",
                  "incorrect_answers": ["It is not compatible with Agile.", "Teams find it difficult to use.", "The output cannot be used for planning."]},

                 {"category": "Software Development",
                  "topic": "Agile",
                  "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "The Lean Muda or seven deadly wastes does not includes __________________.",
                  "correct_answer": "Exploratory Testing",
                  "incorrect_answers": ["Partially done work", "Relearning", "Extra features"]},

                 {"category": "Software Development",
                  "topic": "Agile",
                  "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "When software development is delivered using a linear software development life cycle this means that?",
                  "correct_answer": "The activities of software development occur sequentially from analysis through delivery to testing.",
                  "incorrect_answers": ["All activities to develop the software happen in iterations of small batches.", "The software is created incrementally by building each component starting from any database the proceeding with business logic and presentation layer.", "The testing activities related to software development occur prior to any code being written and delivered."]},

                 {"category": "Software Development",
                  "topic": "Agile",
                  "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "The four value statements within the Agile Manifesto are written in a manner where one set of activities or actions of value are compared to others. This comparison is used to describe?",
                  "correct_answer": "Activities or actions that are considered to have more value compared to those that may have less value.",
                  "incorrect_answers": ["Activities or actions that need to be carried out sequentially so that all of them are undertaken during the delivery.", "Activities or actions that have value in being completed compared to those with no value in being completed.", "Activities or actions that are carried out compared to those that are not carried out."]},

                 {"category": "Software Development",
                  "topic": "Agile",
                  "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "One of the principles of the Agile Manifesto is repeated below: Build projects around motivated individuals. Give them the environment and support they need, and trust them to get the job done. In order to build motivated teams within an environment of support, it is BEST to?",
                  "correct_answer": "Allow teams to self organise into teams with all the skills that are required and hold each other accountable.",
                  "incorrect_answers": ["As people join the organisation they should be allocated to the team that has the highest need for people.", "Have practice leads identify the most capable people from each discipline and assign them to capability roles within teams.", "Have line managers evaluate their staff and assign people to teams based on skills and performance."]},

                 {"category": "Software Development",
                  "topic": "Agile",
                  "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "Agile is a term used for a collective group of ways that teams deliver products and solutions that was formalised as a phrase in 2001. One of the comments made by organisations struggling to adopt agile is that it is only suitable for software development. Which of the below describes one of the earliest created methods that is now considered to be within the agile group of methods and frameworks?",
                  "correct_answer": "A method developed to build cars after observing how supermarkets operate.",
                  "incorrect_answers": ["The process of having a design phase where brainstorming occurs to understand the needs of a product.", "The process of writing tests that define a technical requirement before writing code to deliver the solution.", "The process of developing systems after observing how users interact with current systems."]},

                 {"category": "Software Development",
                  "topic": "Agile",
                  "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "Organisations and teams often fail to understand how the wastes described by Lean regarding physical products relate to code. Which of the below does NOT describe the impact of producing more code than is required to deliver a specific solution to a requirement?",
                  "correct_answer": "The value of additional code and tests created will not decay over time as they can always be used for another work item.",
                  "incorrect_answers": ["Libraries that code relies on may become deprecated or obsolete as core languages are updated and developed.", "Either new people or those who created existing code will have to spend time understanding the code created.", "As time passes the context for why code and tests were created is lost even where extensive documentation is provided."]},

                 {"category": "Software Development",
                  "topic": "Agile",
                  "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "When an Agile team is delivering a solution, which of the following describes the preferred means of interaction with customers and users?",
                  "correct_answer": "The team should directly communicate with customers and users on the delivery of goals identified by the Product Owner.",
                  "incorrect_answers": ["The team should not interact with customers or users, as this should be managed by the relevant support team.", "The team should only interact with the Product Owner and only the Product Owner should interact with customers.", "The customers and stakeholders should tell the team exactly what requirements they want delivered."]},

                 {"category": "Software Development",
                  "topic": "Agile",
                  "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "Teams that apply Agile ways of working are considered better at responding to change. Which aspect of Agile ways of working directly supports this ability to react to change?",
                  "correct_answer": "Using short cycle times of delivery where feedback is regularly received.",
                  "incorrect_answers": ["Ensuring user research is carried out after each major release of the product.", "Having a manager work directly with the team that manages the delivery plan.", "Delivering in phased releases and having lessons learned meetings."]},

                 {"category": "Software Development",
                  "topic": "Agile",
                  "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "When an Agile team has created an iteration or sprint plan with an Agile Product Owner, which of the following statements is NOT true?",
                  "correct_answer": "All work for that iteration or sprint is now fixed and no changes can be made.",
                  "incorrect_answers": ["If the Product Owner identifies a higher priority they can discuss this with the team.", "If an item is undeliverable they will discuss this with the Product Owner.", "The team has forecasted what items they expect to be able to deliver."]},

                 {"category": "Software Development",
                  "topic": "Agile",
                  "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "When an Agile team is self-organising what does this mean?",
                  "correct_answer": "They decide how to deliver items of work that will build the solution.",
                  "incorrect_answers": ["They decide who should get promoted within the organisation.", "They should decide if they need to work in the office or from home.", "They decide what items to be delivered provide value."]},

                 {"category": "Software Development",
                  "topic": "Agile",
                  "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "If every event in Scrum is an opportunity to inspect and adapt, which two contribute to continuous improvement?",
                  "correct_answer": "The retrospective and sprint planning.",
                  "incorrect_answers": ["The daily scrum and retrospective.", "The retrospective and backlog refinement.", "The sprint review and sprint planning."]},

                 {"category": "Software Development",
                  "topic": "Agile",
                  "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "A key principle behind the Agile Manifesto is working at a sustainable pace. You are coaching a team which has a deadline to deliver the first release of their product. To hit the deadline and deliver the required Minimum Viable Product (MVP), which of the following would you advise?",
                  "correct_answer": "The Product Owner should work with the stakeholders to identify the areas of highest value to deliver.",
                  "incorrect_answers": ["The organisation should bring in more people based on the known velocity per person to ensure the team can deliver.", "Testing should be deferred until the end of the delivery phase and delivered once the functionality is complete.", "The organisation should reward the team members that commit to working overtime to hit the deadline."]},

                 {"category": "Software Development",
                  "topic": "Agile",
                  "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "You are working with an agile team, which of the observations below would be an example of them applying an agile way of working?",
                  "correct_answer": "The team will collaborate in groups to deliver all the work for each item.",
                  "incorrect_answers": ["Only the coding work is done and all testing is left until integration.", "All code work is done by programmers before handing to QA for test.", "Each developer completes all work on the item assigned to them."]},

                 {"category": "Software Development",
                  "topic": "Agile",
                  "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "You are working with a new and mixed ability Agile team that requires new apprentices to work with experienced people. How SHOULD you coach the team to manage areas of development for the new apprentices?",
                  "correct_answer": "Coach the team to work in pairs so that those with experience can share their knowledge and build confidence in new colleagues.",
                  "incorrect_answers": ["Arrange for the team to go out for beer and pizza on a weekly or monthly basis to build relationships between team members.", "Where errors occur this should be noted and during the retrospective carry out a root cause analysis of how the problem occurred.", "Include a blame button as part of the release process so that any release that breaks the current build can be assigned to the responsible party."]},

                 {"category": "Software Development",
                  "topic": "Agile",
                  "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "Scrum is a specific framework that is part of the group of methods and frameworks collectively known as Agile. In the Scrum framework there are only three roles that form part of a Scrum team. Of the list below which is considered a role within Scrum?",
                  "correct_answer": "Development Team.",
                  "incorrect_answers": ["Team Lead.", "Product Manager.", "Agile Coach."]},

                 {"category": "Software Development",
                  "topic": "Agile",
                  "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "You are working with an Agile team that holds regular retrospectives. During these retrospectives which of the below would NOT be considered an objective to achieve?",
                  "correct_answer": "Understanding the part of the product that should be delivered next.",
                  "incorrect_answers": ["Discussing and assessing issues around the interpersonal relationships in the team.", "Assessing if there are any improvements in how the team is applying Agile.", "Identifying any areas of skills within the team that could be developed."]},

                 {"category": "Software Development",
                  "topic": "Agile",
                  "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "During backlog refinement, when ensuring an item is ready to be delivered by an Agile team which practice would the team NOT adopt to refine the item?",
                  "correct_answer": "Detail all requirements.",
                  "incorrect_answers": ["Story mapping.", "Impact mapping.", "Specification by example."]},

                 {"category": "Software Development",
                  "topic": "Agile",
                  "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "Agile teams can improve the velocity they achieve during delivery by . . .",
                  "correct_answer": "Improving estimation and collaboration techniques.",
                  "incorrect_answers": ["Carrying out more analysis on items during refinement.", "Increasing the number of people on the team.", "Forecasting more work during planning sessions."]},

                 {"category": "Software Development",
                  "topic": "Agile",
                  "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "Which of the following would NOT be considered a practice that would help a team achieve continuous delivery?",
                  "correct_answer": "Versioning requirements documents.",
                  "incorrect_answers": ["Test Driven Development.", "Three Amigos sessions.", "Continuous integration."]},

                 {"category": "Software Development",
                  "topic": "Agile",
                  "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "Work in progress limits often prevent teams starting new items until those currently in progress are completed. Which of the below frameworks creates a sense of urgency by applying these limits?",
                  "correct_answer": "Kanban.",
                  "incorrect_answers": ["Extreme Programming.", "LeSS.", "Scrum."]},

                 {"category": "Software Development",
                  "topic": "Agile",
                  "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "To avoid scaling issues in Agile deliveries, the organisation SHOULD apply which of the following options?",
                  "correct_answer": "Decompose products into independent goals.",
                  "incorrect_answers": ["Hire multiple Agile coaches.", "Send their staff on an Agile training course.", "Employ system integration consultants."]},


                 ]

